<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Draper</title>
    <link>https://xrsa.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ben Draper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 17:39:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xrsa.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xrsa.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrsa.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Interests I love anything to do with Security, Automation and modern software technologies. If you do want to know anything more about me check out my social networking pages.
Contact Email: ben@xrsa.net
Licensing / Legals Example code and configuration files are public domain, use them as you wish. However, I do not take any responsibility if you decide to use them in your production environment.
Please do not copy my blog content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviving Blog</title>
      <link>https://xrsa.net/2019/11/03/reviving-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrsa.net/2019/11/03/reviving-blog/</guid>
      <description>I am bringing my old blog back to life.
More to come, once I have moved this blog over to a proper CI/CD process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTDB Glusterfs NFS Event Monitor Script</title>
      <link>https://xrsa.net/2015/04/25/ctdb-glusterfs-nfs-event-monitor-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 17:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrsa.net/2015/04/25/ctdb-glusterfs-nfs-event-monitor-script/</guid>
      <description>There is no CTDB monitor script for the GlusterFS NFS implementation as you cannot use the normal NFS event script that comes with CTDB, this is because GlusterFS manages NFS.
Without a proper monitoring script CTDB will not initiate a failover when NFS services fail, below I have created a script to solve this problem.
Code #!/bin/sh # Event script to monitor GlusterFS NFS in a cluster environment # Source: https://xrsa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Block DNS Queries Based on Domain Names via IPtables</title>
      <link>https://xrsa.net/2015/04/01/block-dns-queries-based-on-domain-names-via-iptables/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrsa.net/2015/04/01/block-dns-queries-based-on-domain-names-via-iptables/</guid>
      <description>This code will generate or apply rules for IPtables to block DNS queries based on domain names. I wrote this script because I did not want to manually convert each section of the domain into hex with their respective sizes every time I needed to block a random set of domains.
Example # ./BlockDomain.py Syntax: ./BlockDomain.py gen|apply &amp;lt;DOMAIN&amp;gt;... gen : Generate the required IPTable rules apply : Apply the required IPTable rules (Must be root) Examples: .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Ovirt 3 5 on Centos 7 Hosted Engine</title>
      <link>https://xrsa.net/2015/02/04/installing-ovirt-3-5-on-centos-7-hosted-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 19:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrsa.net/2015/02/04/installing-ovirt-3-5-on-centos-7-hosted-engine/</guid>
      <description>Below are simple step by step instructions for installing the node and getting it configured for the hosted engine using CentOS 7.
Installation Requirements  Installing Hosted Engine on CentOS 7 requires oVirt 3.5.1 Both the node and engine will be running CentOS 7 (Minimal Installation) Ensure the host is fully updated via yum update and rebooted before proceeding  Prerequisites DNS
Ensure you have set up hostnames for the host and engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running VMware ESXi Under Ovirt 3.5</title>
      <link>https://xrsa.net/2014/08/25/running-vmware-esxi-under-ovirt-3.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 15:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xrsa.net/2014/08/25/running-vmware-esxi-under-ovirt-3.5/</guid>
      <description>Getting VMware ESXi to install and run properly under oVirt was an interesting experience. However, it does require patching Qemu.
Please note: I am assuming your oVirt host is Fedora 20. You may skip Step 1 if you have already installed my patched RPMS. However, read on if your curious why the patches are needed.
Step 1 – Patching Qemu Current SRPM for patching Qemu is here: qemu-1.6.2-7.fc20.src.rpm
Please note: I am using the SRPM from the Fedora repository instead of the latest source from Qemu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>